

### Profile

https://facebook.com/brashcrab

Have practically experienced building a startup and fail, important lesson learned, re-evaluate failure and take remedial actions by having a paradigm shift. I strongly believe the glass is neither half full or half empty but our perceptive bias leads to actions which influences the results. Therefore, I believe now, in each problem, there exists an opportunity for "enterprise value" to be created.

## Employment History

Founder & Developer at brashcrab.com

February 2018 - Present

Operations Assistant at Nomad Hospitality Group, Kuching, Sarawak

October 2018 - January 2019

Front desk and Housekeeping multi-tasking role, half of our tenants are Swinburne University students, as such, ad hoc "goodwill ambassador" as well. Co-ordinate all "OTAs" online, eg, Agoda etc, manage marketing channels and rooms inventories

Front Office Assistant at Grand Sentosa Johor Bahru, Johor Bahru

July 2011 - March 2012

Mid-scale business class "budget rates @ 5 star" hotel. Front Office system used is E-hors, learned how "dynamic pricing" of room rates can help achieve a higher ADR.

Team Leader at Lime Tree City Hotel, Kuching, Sarawak

June 2014 - December 2015

Responsible for orientation and on-boarding of new employees. Assigned F&B Bartending role at Limelight Lounge. Acquired "inventory vs pricing" dynamics knowledge, learned how "percentages" reconciliation with menu prices can help generate more "vertical income" for hotel "horizontal" F&B verticals. Framework used, be-spoke framework.

## Education

B.Tech Electrical and Electronics Engineering, Wawasan Open University, Kuching, Sarawak

January 2014 - November 2020

https://github.com/lenomade-brashcrab

## Y Extra-curricular activities

#### **Details**

6694 Matang Jaya, Lrg 2A2 Jalan Matang, Kuching, Sarawak, 93050, Malaysia, 60109757749 lenomade.brashcrab@gmail.co m

Date / Place of birth

1975-08-28

Kuching, Sarawak

Nationality

Malaysian

#### Links

Linkedin

#### **Skills**

Programming

Sales & Marketing

Project Management & Quantification

SEO serp

Networking for Services
Outreach & Exposure

## Languages

English

Bahasa Kebangsaan

Hokkien, Mandarin

# Community Outreach Volunteer at Community Welfare NGO; PPM-007-13-22072017, Kuching, Sarawak

August 2017 – November 2018